this is a quick video showing how to
这是一个简短的视频 展示了如何
freeze a particular frame in shop cut so
冻结Shop Cut中的特定帧 以便
if we have this video here and doesn't
如果我们有这段视频 但没有
even have to be in our timeline
甚至必须在我们的时间线上
necessarily we have a video here we can
我们必须在这里有一段视频 我们可以
play this video and let's say there's a
播放这段视频 假设有一个
certain point like this picture right
像这张图一样的某个点 对吗
here where it's saying 2.0 we want to
这里说的是2.0 我们想要
just freeze on this frame sometimes it's
只是定格在这个画面上 有时它是
called freeze or hold the frame we want
调用冻结或保持我们想要的帧
to actually just export this as a
实际上只是将其导出为
picture so one way you might imagine is
想象一下 你可以想象的一种方式是
to like you can do print screen and then
要喜欢 你可以做印刷屏 然后
crop out the picture but shotgun has a
把照片剪出来 但猎枪有一把
way built in to do this we just go to
要做到这一点 我们只需访问
file when we're at that point in the
文件 当我们在该点上
video and go to export frame and then we
视频并转到导出帧 然后我们
just choose where to put it we'll put it
只要选择放在哪里 我们就会把它放在哪里
on the desktop we'll just call it
在桌面上 我们将其命名为
something miscellaneous here and hit
一些杂乱的东西在这里和击中
save and now that's saved on the desktop
保存 现在已保存在桌面上
as a picture a PNG we can open it up and
作为一张PNG的图片 我们可以打开它
look at just that PNG image so here it
看看这张PNG图片 这里就是
is and then we can also bring it in so
然后我们也可以把它带进来
we can drag and drop it into shot cut or
我们可以将其拖放到截图或
we can go to open file and then we can
我们可以去打开文件然后我们就可以
choose to open that door so that desktop
选择打开那扇门 这样台式机
I'll get a couple things there named
我会在那里买几样东西 命名为
miscellaneous stuff and now this is
杂七杂八的东西 现在这是
actually just the the image so now we
实际上只是图像 所以现在我们
have the video which is right here it's
我有这段视频 就在这里
seven minutes long so we can go to this
七分钟长 这样我们就可以开始了
video in our store so we can find a
我们商店里的视频 这样我们就可以找到一个
certain part of the video or if we want
视频的某些部分 或者如果我们想要
we can come over here and we can just
我们可以来这里 我们可以
put in if I delete this out of the
如果我将其从
timeline we can drag down just the
我们可以将时间线拖到
picture so now just this picture will
所以现在只有这张照片会
play for about two seconds we can make
玩两秒钟我们能做的
it longer or shorter but that is how you
它更长或更短 但这就是你如何
would hold a frame and so we could put
会有一个框架 所以我们可以把
part of the video before and part of the
视频之前的一部分和
video after and essentially hold this
视频之后 基本上拿着这个
frame in between or we could just grab a
或者我们可以只拿一张
picture out and do it that way there two
想象一下 然后这样做 在那里两个
questions leave them below catch you the
问题留在下面 让你明白
next video
下一个视频